"sister's noise" - fripSide​
Covered by Tenjin Kotone​
Original Singer: Nanjou Yoshino
Lyrics/Music: Yaginuma Satoshi​
dare yori mo chikaku ni ita​
You were closer to me than anyone else,​
sono koe wa kikoenakute​
but that voice cannot be heard​
kizami tsuzuketeita toki no naka de​
Yet at long last I was able to meet you​
yatto kimi ni aeta kara​
within the continued ticking of time​
sister's noise sagashi tsuzukeru​
I continue to search for the sister's noise,​
samayou kokoro no basho wo​
because these feelings that have accumlated​
kasane atta​
to where​
kono omoi wa​
my heart wanders​
darenimo kowasenai kara...!​
cannot be destroyed by anyone...!​
machi wa hisoyaka ni kimi wo kakushiteta​
The town surreptitiously hid you​
tadoritsuita basho yomigaeru ano kioku​
The place that you struggled to arrive; those memories that you recalled​
kurikaesareteta shinjitsu wa tooku​
The reality that was repeated was distant​
kimi no sono itami kizukenai mama​
That pain of yours stays unnoticed​
ano hi takushita sono yume ga​
Even if those dreams that​
watashi wo kirisaitemo​
I believed in that day tear me apart​
nani yori mo taisetsu na​
I shall still believe in​
kibou dake shinji tsuranuite​
just my most precious hope​
jibun rashiku ikiru koto​
Living seemingly for myself,​
nani yori mo tsutaetakute​
I want to convey this more than anything else​
umare tsuzukeru kanashimi no itami​
The pain of sorrow that continues to be born:​
sono imi wo kizamu nara​
If I etch in that meaning,​
sister's voice ima todokeru yo​
The sister's voice will now be delivered​
namida sae chikara ni shite​
I'll turn even tears into power and​
tsunagariau​
only our​
tsuyosa dake ga​
connected strength​
subete wo uchinuiteiku​
will pierce everything​
yuugure no houkago itsumo no machinami​
The end of twilight, the usual townscape​
futo miageta sora omoidasu yasashisa wo​
and the skies that you'd casually looked up at: I remember their gentleness​
kimi no manazashi ga kizukasetekureta​
Your gaze made me notice​
yowasa mitomeru yuuki no tsuyosa wo​
the strength of courage to recognize weakness​
atataka na kimi no sono te ga​
Those warm hands of yours​
watashi wo michibiiteku​
are what guide me​
nani yori mo mamoritai​
I want to protect you more than anything,​
kibou ga yami wo tsuranuku kara​
because hope pierces through darkness​
dakishimeta atsui omoi​
Because the hot feelings that I've embraced​
kono sekai o terasu kara​
closely illuminate this world​
hashiri tsuzuke sagashi tsuzuketeita​
Your dreams that I continue to run​
kimi no yume ga ugokidasu​
and search for start to move​
sister's noise hibiki hajimeru​
The sister's noise begins to echo​
takaraka na inochi no imi​
the meaning of a loud life:​
wakatteru yo​
I understand it​
kakegaenai​
Irreplaceable bonds​
kizuna wa kowarenai koto​
do not break ever​
jibun rashiku ikiru koto​
Living seemingly for myself,​
nani yori mo tsutaetakute​
I want to convey this more than anything else​
umare tsuzukeru kanashimi no itami​
The pain of sorrow that continues to be born:​
sono imi wo kizamu nara​
If I etch in that meaning...​
dare yori mo chikaku ni ita​
You were closer to me than anyone else,​
sono koe wa kikoenakute​
but that voice cannot be heard​
kizami tsuzuketeita toki no naka de​
Yet at long last I was able to meet you​
yatto kimi ni aeta kara​
within the continued ticking of time​
sister's noise sagashi tsuzukeru​
I continue to search for the sister's noise,​
samayou kokoro no basho wo​
as I will surely protect the same smile that we both experienced​
kanji atta​
where​
onaji egao​
our hearts​
kanarazu mamotte miseru​
wander to​
mou darenimo kowasenai kara...!​
Because they can no longer be destroyed by anyone...!​